Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory6 Mss.B.B61.inventory06
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents H
  - Hyde, B. Talbot B. (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 22
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 1
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Apr. 12
    - To Boas, 1905 June 1
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 14
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 2
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1908 June 5
    - To Boas, 1908 June 15
    - To Boas, 1915 Mar. 18; 2p.
  - Hyde, F.E. Jr. (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 14
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 May 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 May 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1900 May 28
    - From Boas, 1900 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 May 23
  - Hyde, Walter Woodburn (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 22; 1p.
  - Hyman, G.M. (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 10; 1p.
  - Hyman, J.C. (Box 46)
    - From Boas, 1933 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 10; 2p.
      (Enc: Extract from history of the American Jewish joint distribution committee.)
  - Hypes, J. L. (Box 46)
    - To Boas, 1939 Sept. 5; 1p.